{
  "quizInfo": {
    "Subject": "Enterprise Architecture",
    "Term": "Prelims",
    "Title": "QUIZ REVIEWER",
    "LastModified": "20 September 2024",
    "Authors": [
      "Alexander Oro"
    ],
    "References": [
      "01_Handout_1 and 02_Handout_1"
    ]
  },
  "quizData": [
    {
      "question": "This component of TOGAF provides the \"way of working\" for architects.",
      "answer": "Architecture Development Method",
      "choices": [
        "Architecture Development Method",
        "Architecture Capability Framework",
        "Architecture Content Framework",
        "Enterprise Continuum"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "What does CMMI stand for?",
      "answer": "Capability Maturity Model Integration",
      "choices": [
        "Capability Maturity Model Integration",
        "Capability Minority Model Integration",
        "Capability Maturity Model Incorporation",
        "Capability Maturity Model Intellegent"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "This is considered as the blueprint of an enterprise that provides a common organizational understanding",
      "answer": "Business architecture",
      "choices": [
        "Business architecture",
        "Quality Management",
        "Strategic Management",
        "Business Model Development"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "In MDA, this includes the business requirements and domain model that describes the state of the enterprise where the system will be integrated.",
      "answer": "Computation independent model",
      "choices": [
        "Computation independent model",
        "XML Metadata Interchange",
        "Platform-Independent Model",
        "Platform-Specific Model"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "This pertains to a component of TOGAF that addresses the organization and processes required to establish and operate an architecture within an enterprise",
      "answer": "Architecture Capability Framework",
      "choices": [
        "Architecture Capability Framework",
        "Architecture Development Method",
        "Architecture Content Framework",
        "Enterprise Continuum"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "This process involves the identification of the products and services that the business will sell, the target market, and the anticipated expenses.",
      "answer": "Business Model Development",
      "choices": [
        "Business Model Development",
        "Business Architecture",
        "Quality Management",
        "Strategic Management"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "What does TOGAF stand for?",
      "answer": "The Open Group Architecture Framework",
      "choices": [
        "The Open Group Architecture Framework",
        "Object Management Group",
        "Information Technology Infrastructure Library",
        "Control Objectives for Information and Related Technology"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "It is a framework in which different issues can be easily mapped to understand its nature, implications, and possible solutions.",
      "answer": "Zachman Framework",
      "choices": [
        "Zachman Framework",
        "TOGAF",
        "CMMI",
        "ITIL"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "What does ITIL stand for?",
      "answer": "Information Technology Infrastructure Library",
      "choices": [
        "Information Technology Infrastructure Library",
        "Information Technical Infrastructure Library",
        "Intellegent Technical Infrastructure Library",
        "Intellegent Technology Infrastructure Library"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "It refers to a collection of organizations that has a common set of goals, objectives, and/or a single targeted outcome",
      "answer": "Enterprise",
      "choices": [
        "Enterprise",
        "Internal Drivers",
        "Architecture",
        "Enterprise Architecture"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "This is considered as the key feature of MDA",
      "answer": "Mapping",
      "choices": [
        "Mapping",
        "Sampling",
        "Driving",
        "Cooking"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "It originated as a generic framework and methodology for developing technical architectures.",
      "answer": "TOGAF",
      "choices": [
        "TOGAF",
        "Zachman Framework",
        "CMMI",
        "ITIL"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "What was the Zachman framework formerly called?",
      "answer": "Framework for Information Systems Architecture",
      "choices": [
        "Framework for Information Systems Architecture",
        "Information Technology Infrastructure Library",
        "Intellegent Technical Infrastructure Library",
        "Framework for International Systems Architecture"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "In CMMI, this phase involves processes that are planned, performed, and measured",
      "answer": "Managed",
      "choices": [
        "Managed",
        "Defined",
        "Initial",
        "Optimizing"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "This TOGAF component specifically contains the business, data, application, and information technology architecture.",
      "answer": "Architecture Content Framework",
      "choices": [
        "Architecture Content Framework",
        "Architecture Capability Framework",
        "Architecture Development Method",
        "Enterprise Continuum"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "<br><i>Choose or type 'TR' if the statement is true, or 'FL' if it is false.</i><br><br>The Open Groupâ€™s Standards Information Base (SIB) and the Building Blocks Information Base are reference models in the model-driven architecture.",
      "answer": "FL",
      "choices": [
        "TR",
        "FL"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "<br><i>Choose or type 'TR' if the statement is true, or 'FL' if it is false.</i><br><br>Platform-independent model (PIM) is one of the five (5) abstraction levels in model-driven architecture",
      "answer": "FL",
      "choices": [
        "TR",
        "FL"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "<br><i>Choose or type 'TR' if the statement is true, or 'FL' if it is false.</i><br><br>Data and application architecture are under the enterprise consortium of TOGAF.",
      "answer": "FL",
      "choices": [
        "TR",
        "FL"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "<br><i>Choose or type 'TR' if the statement is true, or 'FL' if it is false.</i><br><br>The information technology (IT) architecture is one of the main components of the Zachman Framework.",
      "answer": "FL",
      "choices": [
        "TR",
        "FL"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "<br><i>Choose or type 'TR' if the statement is true, or 'FL' if it is false.</i><br><br>TOGAF was previously called \"Framework for Information Systems Architecture.\"",
      "answer": "FL",
      "choices": [
        "TR",
        "FL"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "<br><i>Choose or type 'TR' if the statement is true, or 'FL' if it is false.</i><br><br>Model-driven architecture has five (5) abstraction levels.",
      "answer": "FL",
      "choices": [
        "TR",
        "FL"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "<br><i>Choose or type 'TR' if the statement is true, or 'FL' if it is false.</i><br><br>Architecture capability framework provides the \"way of working\" for architects in enterprise architecture.",
      "answer": "FL",
      "choices": [
        "TR",
        "FL"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "<br><i>Choose or type 'TR' if the statement is true, or 'FL' if it is false.</i><br><br>Computation independent model (CIM) includes the business requirements and business model or domain model, which describe the state of the enterprise where the system will be integrated.",
      "answer": "TR",
      "choices": [
        "TR",
        "FL"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "<br><i>Choose or type 'TR' if the statement is true, or 'FL' if it is false.</i><br><br>Platform-specific model (PSM) combines the specifications in the PIM and the details on how a system uses a particular type of platform in the Zachman Framework.",
      "answer": "FL",
      "choices": [
        "TR",
        "FL"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "<br><i>Choose or type 'TR' if the statement is true, or 'FL' if it is false.</i><br><br>Migration planning is included in the TOGAF stepwise cycle approach.",
      "answer": "TR",
      "choices": [
        "TR",
        "FL"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "<br><i>Choose or type 'TR' if the statement is true, or 'FL' if it is false.</i><br><br>TOGAF has a unique stepwise cycle approach when it comes to the method of architecture development.",
      "answer": "TR",
      "choices": [
        "TR",
        "FL"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "<br><i>Choose or type 'TR' if the statement is true, or 'FL' if it is false.</i><br><br>Meta-object facility (MOF) provides a standard repository of the MDA model in enterprise architecture.",
      "answer": "TR",
      "choices": [
        "TR",
        "FL"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "<br><i>Choose or type 'TR' if the statement is true, or 'FL' if it is false.</i><br><br>Common warehouse meta-model (CWM) specifies interfaces that can be used in enabling easy interchange of data and business intelligence metadata between repositories, warehouse tools, and platforms in the TOGAF.",
      "answer": "FL",
      "choices": [
        "TR",
        "FL"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "<br><i>Choose or type 'TR' if the statement is true, or 'FL' if it is false.</i><br><br>The four (4) main components of TOGAF architecture are capability framework, architecture development method, architecture content framework, and model-driven architecture.",
      "answer": "FL",
      "choices": [
        "TR",
        "FL"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "<br><i>Choose or type 'TR' if the statement is true, or 'FL' if it is false.</i><br><br>The Zachman Framework was recognized as the first comprehensive framework for enterprise architecture.",
      "answer": "TR",
      "choices": [
        "TR",
        "FL"
      ]
    }
  ]
}